Black Sparrow Press Collection, 1966-1994 (bulk 1973-1993)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Book Files, 1973-1993
  - #393 War All The Time: Poems 1981-1984, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - #393 War All The Time: Poems 1981-1984, Bukowski, Charles, First Proof (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - #393 War All The Time: Poems 1981-1984, Bukowski, Charles, Second Proof (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - >#393 War All The Time: Poems 1981-1984, Bukowski, Charles, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - #393 War All The Time: Poems 1981-1984, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover copies (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - #394 The Wine of Youth, Fante, John, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - #394 The Wine of Youth, Fante, John, Correspondence, Artwork, Back Matter, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - #394 The Wine of Youth, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - #394 The Wine of Youth, Fante, John, Short Stories Not Used, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - #394 The Wine of Youth, Fante, John, Discarded Materials (Rejected Stories), 1985 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - #394 The Wine of Youth, Fante, John, Final Proof, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - #394 The Wine of Youth, Fante, John, Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - #395 Virginia Dare, Dawson, Fielding, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - #395 Virginia Dare, Dawson, Fielding, Artwork, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - #395 Virginia Dare, Dawson, Fielding, Discarded Materials, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - #395 Virginia Dare, Dawson, Fielding, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - #395 Virginia Dare, Dawson, Fielding, Final Proof, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - #395 Virginia Dare, Dawson, Fielding, Final Corrections by Author, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 2, Folder 3)
  - #395 Virginia Dare,Dawson, Fielding, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover copy, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - #399 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Artwork, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, First Proof (umarked), 1985 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, First Proof (corrected), 1985 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Unbound Copy, 1985 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Mockup (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Mockup (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Hardcover Binding Mockup, 1985 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, Hardcover Blank Mockup, 1985 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - #396 The Secret of Life and Death, Ruppersberg, Allen, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - #397 Alone in a Time of Armies, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Back Matter, 4 Softcover copies, 2 Hardcover copies, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, Artwork, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, First Proof, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, Second Proof, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, Final Proof, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - #398 Out in the World: Selected Letters of Jane Bowles, Bowles, Paul, 4 Hardcover copies, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - #399 Complete Correspondence #6, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - #399 Complete Correspondence #6, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Artwork, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - #399 Complete Correspondence #6, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, First Proof, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - #399 Complete Correspondence #6,Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Second Proof, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - #399 Complete Correspondence #6, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - #400 Yesterday and Today, Layachi, Larbi, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - #400 Yesterday and Today, Layachi, Larbi, Artwork, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - #400 Yesterday and Today, Layachi, Larbi, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - #400 Yesterday and Today, Layachi, Larbi, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - #401 The Vulgar Streak, Lewis, Wyndham, ed. Edwards, Paul, Artwork, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - #401 The Vulgar Streak, Lewis, Wyndham, ed. Edwards, Paul, Discarded Materials (Original Afterword), 1985 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - #401 The Vulgar Streak, Lewis, Wyndham, ed. Edwards, Paul, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - #401 The Vulgar Streak, Lewis, Wyndham, ed. Edwards, Paul, First Proof, 1985 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - #401 The Vulgar Streak, Lewis, Wyndham, ed. Edwards, Paul, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - #402 Parents’ Day, Goodman, Paul, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - #402 Parents’ Day, Goodman, Paul, Artwork, 1985 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - #402 Parents’ Day,, Goodman, Paul, Manuscript and Afterword (by Taylor Stoehn), 1985 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - #402 Parents’ Day,, Goodman, Paul, Final Proof (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - #402 Parents’ Day,, Goodman, Paul, Final Proof (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - #402 Parents’ Day,, Goodman, Paul, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - #402 Parents’ Day,,Goodman, Paul, 2 Hardcover copies, 1985 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, Artwork, 1985 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - 1985 (Box 149, Folder 4, #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, Manuscript (Author Copy),)
  - #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, Manuscript (Office Copy), 1985 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, First Proof, 1985 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, Second Proof, 1985 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, Final Proof, 1985 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - #403 New Spaces: Poems 1975-1983, Oppenheimer, Joel, Drawing from Life: Poems Used in New Spaces, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Drawing from Life: Poems Used in New Spaces, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Drawing from Life: Poems Not Used in New Spaces, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles, Fante, John, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles, Fante, John, Artwork, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles, Fante, John, Editor’s Manuscript, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles, Fante, John, Discarded Materials, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles, Fante, John, First Proof, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles, Fante, John, Second Proof, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - #404 The Road To Los Angeles Fante, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - #405 The Color of Air,Sanford, John, Artwork, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, Manuscript, Part I (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, Manuscript, Part I (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, Manuscript, Part II (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, Manuscript, Part II (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, First Proof, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, Second Proof, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, Discarded Materials (First Draft), 1985 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - #405 The Color of Air, Sanford, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - #406 John Register, Browning, Jeffrey, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - #406 John Register, Browning, Jeffrey, First Draft, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - #406 John Register, Browning, Jeffrey, First Manuscript, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - #406 John Register, Browning, Jeffrey, Final Manuscript, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - #406 John Register, Browning, Jeffrey, Edited Proof, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - #406 John Register, Browning, Jeffrey, Unbound Signed Tip-in Pages (18), 1985 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - #406 John Register, Browning, Jeffrey, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - #407 1933 Was a Bad Year, Fante, John, Artwork, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - #407 1933 Was a Bad Year, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - #407 1933 Was a Bad Year, Fante, John, Second Proof, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - #407 1933 Was a Bad Year, Fante, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - #408 The Letters of D.H. Lawerence and Amy Lowell 1914-1925, ed. Cushman, Keith, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - #408 The Letters of D.H. Lawerence and Amy Lowell 1914-1925, ed. Cushman, Keith, Artwork, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - #408 The Letters of D.H. Lawerence and Amy Lowell 1914-1925, ed. Cushman, Keith, Manuscript, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - #408 The Letters of D.H. Lawerence and Amy Lowell 1914-1925, ed. Cushman, Keith, First Proof, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - #408 The Letters of D.H. Lawerence and Amy Lowell 1914-1925, ed. Cushman, Keith, Second Proof, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - #408 The Letters of D.H. Lawerence and Amy Lowell 1914-1925, ed. Cushman, Keith, 3 Hardcover copies, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - #409 A European Education, Mudd, Harvey, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - #409 A European Education, Mudd, Harvey, Artwork, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - #409 A European Education, Mudd, Harvey, Artwork, First Manuscript, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - #409 A European Education, Mudd, Harvey, Artwork, Second Manuscript, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - #409 A European Education, Mudd, Harvey, First Proofs (Revised), 1986 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - #409 A European Education, Mudd, Harvey, First Proofs (Revised), Final Proofs, Unbound Copy, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - #410 Rotting Hill, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - #410 Rotting Hill, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - #410 Rotting Hill, Lewis, Wyndham, Copy of Original Text (1952), 1986 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - #410 Rotting Hill, Lewis, Wyndham, Revised Manuscript, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - #410 Rotting Hill, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - #410 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - #410 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Artwork, 1986 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - #410 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, First Manuscript (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - #410 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, First Manuscript (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985,Eshleman, Clayton, Discarded Material (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Discarded Material (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - 411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Final Manuscript (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Final Manuscript (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Final Manuscript First Proof (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Final Manuscript First Proof (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Second Proof (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, Second Proof (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - #411 The Name Encanyoned River: Selected Poems 1960-1985, Eshleman, Clayton, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1986 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Artwork, 1986 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Manuscript (Section A), 1986 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Manuscript (Section B-C), 1986 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Manuscript (Section D-H), 1986 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, First Proof (Section A) and Discarded Material, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, First Proof (Section B), 1986 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, First Proof (Section C-H), 1986 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Second Proof (Section A), 1986 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Third Proof (Section A), Second Proof (Section B), 1986 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Fourth Proof (Section A), Third Proof (Section B)—Revision 1, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Fourth Proof (Section A), Third Proof (Section B)—Revision 2, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Index only, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Index only, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, Final Proofs, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - #412 An Invisible Spectator: A Biography of Paul Bowles, Miller, Jeffrey, 3 Hardcover copies, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - #413 Selected Poems: 1958-1984,, Wieners, John, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - #413 Selected Poems: 1958-1984,, Wieners, John, Artwork, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - #413 Selected Poems: 1958-1984,, Wieners, John, Manuscript, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - #413 Selected Poems: 1958-1984,, Wieners, John, Manuscript, First Proof, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - #413 Selected Poems: 1958-1984,,Wieners, John, Second Proof, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - #413 Selected Poems: 1958-1984,,Wieners, John, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover copy, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - #413 Selected Poems: 1958-1984,,Wieners, John, 2 Hardcover copies, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - #414 Gold in Your Eye: A New Year’s Greeting,,Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 3 Hardcover copies, 2 Softcover copies, Signed Tip-ins (17), 1986 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - #415 Caliph’s Design,,Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Artwork, Notes on Illustrations, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - #415 Caliph’s Design, Lewis, Wyndham, Afterword and Notes (1986), 1919 Manuscript copy (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - #415 Caliph’s Design Lewis, Wyndham, First Proof, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - #415 Caliph’s Design, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proof, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - #415 Caliph’s Design, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover copy, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover copy; 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - #416 Waters of Darkness, Sanford, John, Artwork, Ephemera, 1986 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - #416 Waters of Darkness, Sanford, John, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - #416 Waters of Darkness, Sanford, John, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - #416 Waters of Darkness, Sanford, John, First Proof, 1986 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - #416 Waters of Darkness, Sanford, John, Second Proof, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - #416 Waters of Darkness, Sanford, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - #417 The Rings of Saturn, Wakoski, Diane, Correspondence, Artwork, Back Matter, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - #417 The Rings of Saturn, Wakoski, Diane, Manuscript, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - #417 The Rings of Saturn, Wakoski, Diane, First Proof, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - #417 The Rings of Saturn, Wakoski, Diane, Second Proof, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - #417 The Rings of Saturn, Wakoski, Diane, Rejected Poems, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - #417 The Rings of Saturn, Wakoski, Diane, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - #418 West of Rome, Fante, John, Correspondence, Artwork, 1986 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - #418 West of Rome, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1986 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - #418 West of Rome, Fante, John, First Proof, 1986 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - #418 West of Rome, Fante, John, Second Proof, 1986 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - #418 West of Rome, Fante, John, 4 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1986 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - #419 You Get So Alone at Times That it Just Makes Sense, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, Artwork, Back Matter, 1986 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - #419 You Get So Alone at Times That it Just Makes Sense, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript, 1986 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - #419 You Get So Alone at Times That it Just Makes Sense, Bukowski, Charles, First Proof, 1986 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - #419 You Get So Alone at Times That it Just Makes Sense, Bukowski, Charles, 4 Hardcover copies, 1986 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, Artwork, 1986 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, Manuscript (1 of 4), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, Manuscript (2 of 4), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, Manuscript (3 of 4), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, Manuscript (4 of 4), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, 2 Hardcover copies, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - #420 Robert Duncan: A Descriptive Bibliography, Berthold, Robert, 1 Hardcover copies, 1986 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - #421 Collected Poems of Marsden Hartley, Scott, Gail R., Correspondence, Artwork, 1987 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - #421 Collected Poems of Marsden Hartley, Scott, Gail R., Manuscript (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - #421 Collected Poems of Marsden Hartley, Scott, Gail R., Manuscript (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - #421 Collected Poems of Marsden Hartley, Scott, Gail R., Second Proof (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - #421 Collected Poems of Marsden Hartley, Scott, Gail R., Second Proof (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - #421 Collected Poems of Marsden Hartley, Scott, Gail R., 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - #422 Luck: A New Year’s Greeting, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, 2 Hardcover copies, 2 Softcover, 1987 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Artwork, Back Matter, 1987 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, First Proof, 1987 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Second Proof, 1987 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Third Proof (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Third Proof (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - #423 Complete Correspondence #7, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Artwork, 1987 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript, 1987 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, First Proof (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, First Proof (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proof (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proof (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, Final Proof (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, Final Proof (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - #424 Men without Art, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - #425 Disordered Ideas, Clark, Tom, Correspondence, Artwork, 1987 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - #425 Disordered Ideas, Clark, Tom, Manuscripts, 1987 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - #425 Disordered Ideas, Clark, Tom, First Proofs, 1987 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - #425 Disordered Ideas, Clark, Tom, Second Proofs, 1987 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - #426 Not This Island Music, Kelly, Robert, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - #426 Not This Island Music, Kelly, Robert, Artwork, Insert for Deluxe Edition, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - #426 Not This Island Music, Kelly, Robert, Manuscript, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - #426 Not This Island Music, Kelly, Robert, Third Proof, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - #426 Not This Island Music, Kelly, Robert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - #427 Complete Correspondence #8, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Correspondence, Artwork, 1987 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - #427 Complete Correspondence #8, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Manuscript, 1987 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - #427 Complete Correspondence #8, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - #428 The Musician, Shelnutt, Eve, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - #428 The Musician, Shelnutt, Eve, Correspondence, Artwork, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - #428 The Musician, Shelnutt, Eve, Manuscript, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - #428 The Musician, Shelnutt, Eve, First Proof, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - #428 The Musician, Shelnutt, Eve, First Proof, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - #428 The Musician, Shelnutt, Eve, Second Proof, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - #428 The Musician, Shelnutt, Eve, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 6)